Guide to the James Perkins papers,1963-1969.
Perkins, James papers,1963-1969.
- Series II. 1965-1967
  - Student Government Executive Board., 1965-1967 (Box 13, Folder 20)
  - Cornell Daily Sun., 1965-1967 (Box 13, Folder 21)
  - Sororities., 1967 (Box 13, Folder 22)
  - WVBR., 1965-1966 (Box 13, Folder 23)
    Stragow, Darry Allen; Kahn, Alfred E. Cornell Radio Guild, Inc.
  - Proctor., 1966-1967 (Box 13, Folder 24)
    Travis, Richard M.; Dancis, Bruce D.; George, Lowell T. Student conduct.
  - Secretary of the University., 1966-1967 (Box 13, Folder 25)
    Rideout, Blanchard L.
  - University Press., 1967 (Box 13, Folder 26)
  - Cornell University Libraries., 1965-1967 (Box 13, Folder 27)
    Healey, George H.; Guerlac, Henry; Reichmann, Felix; McCarthy, Stephen A.; Shepherd, Giles F.; Hollister, Solomon C. LaForte Collection; Library Board.
  - Cornell University Libraries., 1965-1967 (Box 13, Folder 28)
    McCarthy, Stephen A.; Dean, Arthur H.; Sproull, Robert L.; Corson, Dale R.; Healey, George H.; Colman, Gould P. Library Board; Blancheteau Collection; Library budget.
  - Cornell University Libraries., 1965-1967 (Box 13, Folder 29)
    McCarthy, Stephen A.; Corson, Dale R.; Dean, Arthur H. Library Board; Arthur H. Dean Book Collecting Contest.
  - Cornell University Libraries., 1965-1967 (Box 13, Folder 30)
    Kirby, Allan P.; McCarthy, Stephen A.; Dean, Arthur H. Library Board.
  - Announcements., 1966-1967 (Box 13, Folder 31)
  - Regional History and University Archives. Fox, Edith M.; Finch, C. Herbert; Bess, James L. Program in Oral History., 1965-1966 (Box 13, Folder 32)
  - University Committee on the Arts., 1965-1967 (Box 13, Folder 33)
    Leavitt, Thomas W.; Kelly, Burnham; Morison, Robert S. Rockefeller Foundation.
  - University Committee on the Arts., 1965-1967 (Box 13, Folder 34)
    Guerlac, Henry; Kelly, Burnham.
  - WHCU., 1965-1966 (Box 13, Folder 35)
  - Photographic Science., 1967 (Box 13, Folder 36)
    Dameron, Maclean. Microfilming.
  - Willard Straight Hall., 1965-1966 (Box 13, Folder 37)
    Willers, Diedrich K. Retirement funds.
  - Personnel Office., 1965-1967 (Box 13, Folder 38)
  - Munschauer, John L. University Placement Office., 1966 (Box 13, Folder 39)
  - Andrew Dickson White Museum of Art., 1965-1967 (Box 13, Folder 40)
    Leavitt, Thomas W.; Johnson, Herbert F.; Young, Martie W.; Kelly, Burnham; Starke, Ralph G.; Bache, Harold L. Museum directorship.
  - Financial Aids Office., 1965-1967 (Box 13, Folder 41)
  - University Relations., 1965-1967 (Box 13, Folder 42)
    Marcham, John. Cornell Newsletters.
  - University Relations., 1965-1967 (Box 13, Folder 43)
    Marcham, John; Eager, George B. Cornell Newsletters.
  - University Relations., 1965-1967 (Box 13, Folder 44)
    Arden, Kelvin J.; Marcham, John; Cornell Newsletters.
  - University Relations., 1965-1967 (Box 13, Folder 45)
    Marcham, John; Eager, George B.
  - Cornell Airplane., 1965-1967 (Box 14, Folder 1)
    Rockefeller, Laurance S.
  - Cornell Airplane., 1965-1967 (Box 14, Folder 2-4)
  - University Faculty., 1962-1965 (Box 14, Folder 5)
    Malott, Deane W. Barnes Hall.
  - University Faculty, Meetings and Agendas., 1966-1967 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - University Faculty, Minutes., 1965-1967 (Box 14, Folder 7-10)
  - Dean of the Faculty., 1965-1967 (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - University Faculty., 1965-1967 (Box 14, Folder 12)
    Murphy, Royse P.; Cook, Alice H. Human Rights Committee; United States Selective Service; Troian Horse; Faculty Committee on Student Affairs (Parrish Report).
  - University Faculty., 1965-1967 (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - Faculty Committees., 1965-1967 (Box 14, Folder 14-15)
    University Faculty. Includes Faculty Committee on Student Affairs (Parrish Report)
  - Faculty Council., 1965-1967 (Box 14, Folder 16-18)
    University Faculty; United States Selective Service; Student conduct.
  - University Lectures., 1966-1967 (Box 14, Folder 19)
    Kennan, George F.; Lindsay, John V.
  - Prizes., 1966-1967 (Box 14, Folder 20)
  - Student Conduct., 1967 (Box 14, Folder 21)
  - Student Affairs., 1965-1967 (Box 14, Folder 22)
    Pike, Nelson.
  - Calendar., 1966 (Box 14, Folder 23)
  - Music., 1965-1967 (Box 14, Folder 24)
  - Economic Status of the Faculty., 1965-1967 (Box 14, Folder 25)
    Parking.
  - Necrology., 1965-1967 (Box 14, Folder 26)
  - Necrology., 1965-1967 (Box 14, Folder 27)
  - Academic Freedom and Tenure., 1960-1966 (Box 14, Folder 28)
  - Pensions and Retirement., 1966 (Box 14, Folder 29)
  - Faculty Salaries., 1965-1967 (Box 14, Folder 30)
  - New York State College of Agriculture., 1965-1966 (Box 14, Folder 31)
    Adams, Morton; Robison, Howard W. Bankhead - Jones Act.
  - New York State College of Agriculture., 1965-1966 (Box 14, Folder 32)
    Adams, Morton; Palm, Charles E.; King, Joseph P.; Robison, Howard W.; Dow, John G.; Freeman, Orville L. American Assn. of State Universities and Land Grant Colleges; United States Dept. of Agriculture - Cooperative Extension Service; Federal budget cuts.
  - New York State College of Agriculture., 1965-1966 (Box 14, Folder 33)
    Palm, Charles E. Federal budget cuts.
  - New York State College of Agriculture., 1965-1966 (Box 14, Folder 34)
    Tyler, Howard S.; Palm, Charles E. College of Agriculture faculty.
  - New York State College of Agriculture., 1966-1967 (Box 14, Folder 35)
    Palm, Charles E.; Adams, Morton. College of Agriculture faculty; President's Committee to Study the New York State College of Agriculture.
  - New York State College of Agriculture., 1966-1967 (Box 14, Folder 36)
    President's Committee to Study the New York State College of Agriculture.
  - New York State College of Agriculture., 1966-1967 (Box 14, Folder 37)
    President's Committee to Study the New York State College of Agriculture; Departmental Evaluation survey.
  - New York State College of Agriculture., 1966-1967 (Box 14, Folder 38)
    Palm, Charles E.; Adams, Morton. National Academy of Sciences - National Research Council Agricultural Board.
  - Departments, College of Agriculture. Olson, Gerald W.; Brady, Nyle C., 1965-1967 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Departments, College of Agriculture., 1965-1967 (Box 15, Folder 2)
    Ward, William B.; Gates, Albert H.; Brady, Nyle C.; Linscott, Dean L.; Feuer, Reeshon.
  - Laboratory of Ornithology., 1966-1967 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - New York State Cooperative Extension Service., 1966-1967 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - College of Architecture., 1965-1967 (Box 15, Folder 5)
    Kelly, Burnham; Corson, Dale R. College of Architecture faculty; New York City Field Station; Green Dragon Day.
  - College of Architecture., 1965-1967 (Box 15, Folder 6)
    Kelly, Burnham; Fisher, Jack C.; Parsons, Kermit C.; Detweiler, Henry A. College of Architecture faculty; Architectural Review Board; Jacob Hirsch Trust.
  - College of Arts and Sciences., 1965-1967 (Box 15, Folder 7)
    Brown, Stuart M.; Kahin, George McT.; McCleery, William T. College of Arts and Sciences faculty; Social Sciences Building; Educational Policy Committee.
  - College of Arts and Sciences., 1965-1967 (Box 15, Folder S)
    Brown, Stuart M. Lane Cooper Scholarships.
  - College of Arts and Sciences., 1965-1967 (Box 15, Folder 9)
    Brown, Stuart M. Advisory Board for Underclassmen; Humanities Council.
  - Departments, College of Arts and Sciences., 1965-1967 (Box 15, Folder 10)
    Parrish, Stephen M. Rockefeller Foundation; Ford Foundation; Six Year Ph.D. Program; Residential Club fire.
  - Departments, College of Arts and Sciences., 1965-1967 (Box 15, Folder 11)
    McConkey, James R.; Brown, Stuart M.; Voznesensky, Andrei; Demorest, Jean-Jacques; Freccero, John; Parrish, Stephen M.; Konvitz, Milton R. Six Year Ph.D. Program; University Theatre.
  - Chemistry., 1965-1967 (Box 15, Folder 12)
    Olin, John M.; Josephs, Devereux C.; Plane, Robert A.; Scheraga, H.A.; Queeny, Edgar M. National Science Foundation; Clark Hall.
  - Economics., 1966-1967 (Box 15, Folder 13)
    Morse, Chandler; Liu, Ta-Chung; Kahn, Alfred E. Social Sciences Building.
  - Dept. of Far Eastern Studies., 1965-1966 (Box 15, Folder 14)
    Kahin, George McT. Vietnam.
  - Department of History., 1966 (Box 15, Folder 15)
  - Computing Center., 1965-1967 (Box 15, Folder 16)
    Long, Franklin A. Dept. of Computer Science; Computers.
  - Dept. of Modern Languages., 1966 (Box 15, Folder 17)
  - Music., 1965-1967 (Box 15, Folder 18)
    Sokol, Thomas A.; Husa, Karel.
  - Sage Chapel Choir., 1966-1967 (Box 15, Folder 19)
  - Dept. of Romance Literature., 1966 (Box 15, Folder 20)
    Demorest, Jean- Jacques.
  - Physics., 1966-1967 (Box 15, Folder 21)
    Wilson, Robert R.; Gold, Thomas. Center for Radiophysics and Space Research.
  - Sociology and Anthropology., 1966-1967 (Box 15, Folder 22)
    Shen, T.H. Social Sciences Building.
  - Center for International Studies., 1965-1967 (Box 15, Folder 23)
    Corson, Dale R.; Einaudi, Mario; Beckmann, George M. Ford Foundation.
  - Center for International Studies., 1965-1967 (Box 15, Folder 24)
    Muller, Steven; Stycos, Jose Mayone. Ford Foundation; Cornell Latin American Year.
  - College of Engineering., 1966-1967 (Box 15, Folder 25)
  - College of Engineering., 1966-1967 (Box 15, Folder 26)
    Schultz, Andrew. United States Dept. of Health, Education and Welfare - Public Health Service.
  - College of Engineering, Minutes of the Faculty., 1965-1967 (Box 15, Folder 27)
  - New York State College of Home Economics. Canoyer, Helen G. Organizational Committee of the College of Home Economics., 1966-1967 (Box 15, Folder 28)
  - New York State College of Home Economics. Canoyer, Helen G.; Sproull, Robert L. Organizational Committee of the College of Home Economics., 1966-1967 (Box 15, Folder 29)
  - New York State College of Home Economics., 1966-1967 (Box 15, Folder 30-31)
  - New York State College of Home Economics., 1965-1966 (Box 15, Folder 32)
    Canoyer, Helen G. "Campus Academic Plan for the State College of Home Economics at Cornell University."
  - New York State College of Home Economics., 1965-1966 (Box 15, Folder 33)
    Canoyer, Helen G.; Personius, Catherine J. College of Home Economics faculty.
  - New York State College of Home Economics., 1965-1966 (Box 15, Folder 34)
    Wood, Mary B. College of Home Economics faculty.
  - New York State Veterinary College., 1965-1967 (Box 15, Folder 35-37)
    Poppensiek, George C. Veterinary College faculty.
  - Cornell University Medical College and New York Hospital., 1965-1966 (Box 15, Folder 38)
    Deitrick, John E.; Hinsey, Joseph C.; Luckey, E. Hugh.
  - Cornell University Medical College and New York Hospital., 1965-1966 (Box 15, Folder 39)
    Hinsey, Joseph C.; Deitrick, John E. Society of the New York Hospital.
  - Cornell University Medical College and New York Hospital., 1965-1966 (Box 15, Folder 40)
    Whitney, John Hay; Hinsey, Joseph C. Executive Faculty.
  - Cornell University Medical College and New York Hospital., 1965-1966 (Box 15, Folder 41)
    Deitrick, John E. Executive Faculty.
  - Cornell University Medical College and New York Hospital., 1965-1966 (Box 15, Folder 42)
    American Medical Association; Association of American Medical Colleges.
  - Cornell University Medical College and New York Hospital. Hinsey, Joseph C.; Luckey, E. Hugh; Deitrick, John E., 1966-1967 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Cornell University Medical College and New York Hospital., 1966-1967 (Box 16, Folder 2)
    Deitrick, John E. Executive Faculty; Bellevue Hospital.
  - Cornell University Medical College and New York Hospital., 1966-1967 (Box 16, Folder 3)
    Deitrick, John E.; Vanderwarker, Richard D. Executive Faculty.
  - Cornell University Medical College and New York Hospital Joint Administrative Board., 1965-1967 (Box 16, Folder 4-5)
  - Cornell Medical Center - New York Hospital, Sloan-Kettering Institute., 1965-1967 (Box 16, Folder 6-7)
    Vanderwarker, Richard D.
  - Cornell University Medical College and New York Hospital Executive Faculty Minutes., 1965-1967 (Box 16, Folder 8-10)
  - Cornell Medical Center - New York Hospital, Sloan-Kettering Institute Minutes., 1965-1967 (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - Law School., 1965-1967 (Box 16, Folder 12)
    Forrester, Ray; Ritchie, John; Warren, Ernest N.; Dean, Arthur H. American Bar Association; Law School faculty.
  - New York State School of Industrial and Labor Relations., 1965-1967 (Box 16, Folder 13)
    Moore, David G.; Whyte, William Foote.
  - New York State School of Industrial and Labor Relations. Whyte, William Foote; Moore, David G.; Risley, Robert F. Academic Plan; Faculty., 1965-1967 (Box 16, Folder 14)
  - Cornell University Medical College and New York Hospital School of Nursing., 1965-1966 (Box 16, Folder 15)
  - Graduate School of Business and Public Administration., 1965-1966 (Box 16, Folder 16)
    Carmichael, William D.; Sanders, Irwin T.; Roche, Marcel. Alfred P. Sloan Foundation; Ford Foundation; Latin American Internship Program.
  - School of Hotel Administration., 1966-1967 (Box 16, Folder 17)
    Beck, Robert A.; MacLennan, H. Alexander. Cornell Society of Hotelmen.
  - School of Education., 1965-1967 (Box 16, Folder 18)
    Johnson, Mauritz. School of Education faculty; Five College Project.
  - School of Education., 1965-1967 (Box 16, Folder 19)
    Hixon, Lawrence B.; Stutz, Frederick H. Cornell University Educational Placement Bureau; Special Committee of the University Faculty on Education; School of Education faculty.
  - School of Education., 1965-1967 (Box 16, Folder 20)
    Stutz, Frederick H.; Gowin, D.B. School of Education faculty; Five College Project; Research and graduate training.
  - School of Education., 1965-1967 (Box 16, Folder 21)
    Stutz, Frederick H. Inter-University Program.
  - Graduate School of Nutrition., 1966-1967 (Box 16, Folder 22)
    Barnes,; Richard H.
  - Graduate School., 1965-1967 (Box 16, Folder 23-27)
    Cooke, W. Donald. Graduate School faculty.
  - Division of Unclassified Students., 1966-1967 (Box 16, Folder 28)
  - Division of Biological Sciences., 1965-1967 (Box 16, Folder 29)
    Morison, Robert S.
  - Military Science and Tactics, ROTC., 1965-1967 (Box 16, Folder 30)
    Waters, Martin J.; Yancey, Thomas R.
  - Air ROTC., 1965-1967 (Box 16, Folder 31)
  - Physical Education and Athletics., 1965-1967 (Box 16, Folder 32)
    Kane, Robert J.; Musick, Jack; Harkness, Ned. Ivy League; National Collegiate Athletic Association.
  - Ivy League., 1965-1967 (Box 16, Folder 33)
    Brewster, Kingman; Kirk, Gray son. American Broadcasting Company; Eligibility.
  - Naval ROTC., 1965-1967 (Box 16, Folder 34)
    Dukes, William P.
  - Matters Relating to All ROTC., 1965-1967 (Box 16, Folder 35)
    Buse, Henry W.
  - Cornell Aeronautical Laboratory., 1965-1967 (Box 16, Folder 36)
    Kahn, Alfred E.; Ross, Ira G.; Schoellkopf, Paul A.; Long, Franklin A. Faculty Council Committee on Relations Between Cornell University and Cornell Aeronautical Laboratory.
  - Cornell Aeronautical Laboratory., 1965-1967 (Box 16, Folder 37)
    Ross, Ira G.; Moffitt, Henry K.
  - Cornell Aeronautical Laboratory., 1965-1967 (Box 16, Folder 38-39)
  - Cornell Aeronautical Laboratory, Minutes., 1965-1966 (Box 16, Folder 40)
  - Cornell Aeronautical Laboratory, Finances., 1965-1966 (Box 16, Folder 41)
  - Summer Session., 1965-1967 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - University Health Services., 1966-1967 (Box 17, Folder 2)
    Moore, Norman S.
  - CURW., 1965-1967 (Box 17, Folder 3)
    Rogers, William W.; Lewis, W. Jack. Cornell-Brazil Study and Involvement Project.
  - CURW., 1965-1967 (Box 17, Folder 4)
    Lewis, W. Jack; Rogers, William W.; Smith, John Lee. John R. Mott Centennial Celebration; Cornell-Brazil Study and Involvement Project.
  - CURW., 1965-1967 (Box 17, Folder 5)
    Lewis, W. Jack.
  - CURW., 1965-1967 (Box 17, Folder 6)
    Lewis, W. Jack; Rogers, William W.; Camara, Dom Helder. Rockefeller Brothers Fund; Cornell-Brazil Study and Involvement Project; Central Intelligence Agency.
  - CURW., 1965-1967 (Box 17, Folder 7)
    Wood, Franklin S.; Arrowsmith, William.
  - Danforth Foundation., 1966-1967 (Box 17, Folder S)
    Wise, W. Max; Bornholdt, Laura.
  - Alumni Fund., 1965-1966 (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - Alumni Office., 1965-1967 (Box 17, Folder 10-11)
    Bradley, Hunt.
  - Cornell Clubs., 1965-1967 (Box 17, Folder 12)
    Batt, Jerome A.; Bradley, Hunt.
  - Scholarships, Grants, Gifts., 1965-1967 (Box 17, Folder 13)
    Olin, John M.; Dean, Arthur H.; Kahn, Alfred E.; Kettering, Eugene W.
  - Messenger Lectures., 1965-1967 (Box 17, Folder 14)
    Jouvet, M.; Gardner, Helen; Detweiler, Henry A.
  - SUNY., 1966-1967 (Box 17, Folder 15)
    Gould, Samuel B.; Corson, Dale R.; Olds, Glenn A.; Palm, Charles E.
  - New York State Education Dept., 1965-1967 (Box 17, Folder 16)
    Alien, James E.; Nyquist, Ewald B. Advisory Council on Higher Education; Higher Education Facilities Act.
  - New York State Education Dept., 1965-1967 (Box 17, Folder 17)
    Alien, James E.
  - New York State Education Dept., 1965-1967 (Box 17, Folder 18)
    Nyquist, Ewald B.; Kille, Frank R.
  - New York State Education Dept., 1965-1967 (Box 17, Folder 19)
    Alien, James E.; Nyquist, Ewald B.
  - New York State Education Dept., 1965-1967 (Box 17, Folder 20)
    Higher Education Facilities Act.
  - Regents., 1964-1967 (Box 17, Folder 21)
    Alien, James E. Professorships.
  - Regents., 1964-1967 (Box 17, Folder 22)
    Professorships; Einstein Chair; Schweitzer Chair.
  - A (Excluding American.), 1965-1967 (Box 17, Folder 23)
    Adam, John H.; Adams, Norton; Muller, Steven. Advanced Research Projects Agency; Agency for International Development.
  - A (Excluding American)., 1965-1967 (Box 17, Folder 24)
    Ashby, Eric. Association of Governing Boards of Universities and Colleges.
  - A (Excluding American)., 1965-1967 (Box 17, Folder 25)
    Glennan, T. Keith. Associated Universities, Inc.
  - American., 1965-1967 (Box 17, Folder 26)
    Streib, Gordon F. American Civil Liberties Union; American Association of University Women; American Association of University Professors.
  - American., 1965-1967 (Box 17, Folder 27)
    American Institute of Indian Studies.
  - American Council on Education., 1966-1967 (Box 17, Folder 28-32)
    Wilson, Logan.
  - American Council on Education., 1965-1966 (Box 17, Folder 33-36)
    Wilson, Logan. American Council on Education Commission on International Education.
  - American Council on Education., 1965-1966 (Box 17, Folder 37)
    Wilson, Logan; Kizilbash, Mehdi. American Council on Education Commission on International Education.
  - American School of Oriental Research., 1965 (Box 18, Folder 1)
    Detweiler, Henry A.
  - Applications for Jobs., 1965-1966 (Box 18, Folder 2-3)
  - Association of American Colleges., 1964-1967 (Box 18, Folder 4)
    Wormald, F.L.; Davidson, Carter; Sullivan, Richard H.
  - Association of American Universities., 1965-1967 (Box 18, Folder 5)
    McCurdy, Charles P.
  - Association of American Universities., 1965-1967 (Box 18, Folder 6)
    Brewster, Kingman; McCurdy, Charles P.; Bowen, Howard R.
  - Association of American Universities., 1965-1967 (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Association of American Universities., 1965-1967 (Box 18, Folder 8)
    McCurdy, Charles P. Students for a Democratic Society (SDS).
  - Association of Colleges and Universities of the State of New York., 1965-1967 (Box 18, Folder 9)
    Lord, Clifford; Ingalls, Lester W.; Mortola, Edward J.
  - Association of Colleges and Universities of the State of New York., 1965-1967 (Box 18, Folder 10)
    Lord, Clifford; Ingalls, Lester W.
  - B-BN Miscellaneous., 1965-1967 (Box 18, Folder 11)
    Balogun, George Tunde; Barnette, Stuart; Beckmann, George M.; Beggs, Robert W. University Peace Days.
  - B-BN Miscellaneous. Benitez, Jaime; Bethe, Rose; Saperstone, David A., 1965-1967 (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - B-BN Miscellaneous., 1965-1967 (Box 18, Folder 13)
    Biddle, Louisa Copeland; Black, Max; Blackall, Eric Albert; Blanding, Sarah Gibson; Block, Joseph L.
  - BO-BZ Miscellaneous., 1965-1967 (Box 18, Folder 14)
    Boyd, Julian P.; Brewster, Kingman; Bronfenbrenner, Urie.
  - BO-BZ Miscellaneous., 1965-1967 (Box 18, Folder 15)
    Bryan, Julien; Bundy, McGeorge.
  - C-CN Miscellaneous., 1965-1967 (Box 18, Folder 16)
  - C-CN Miscellaneous., 1965-1967 (Box 18, Folder 17)
    Caplan, Harry. Student conduct.
  - C-CN Miscellaneous., 1965-1967 (Box 18, Folder 18)
    Clark, Hays Lawrence.
  - C-CN Miscellaneous., 1965-1967 (Box 18, Folder 19)
    Requardt, Gustav J.; Kinne, Birge W.
  - CO-CZ Miscellaneous., 1965-1967 (Box 18, Folder 20)
    Collins, Samuel W.
  - CO-CZ Miscellaneous., 1965-1967 (Box 18, Folder 21)
    Newton, Quigg; Conant, James B.
  - CO-CZ Miscellaneous., 1965-1967 (Box 18, Folder 22)
    Covey, Winton; Curtiss, W. David. Peace Corps.
  - Clark Hall of Science Dedication., 1965 (Box 18, Folder 23)
  - Clark, Van Alan and Edna., 1964-1967 (Box 18, Folder 24)
    Clark Hall; Edna McConnell Clark Foundation.
  - Carnegie Corporation., 1965-1967 (Box 18, Folder 25)
    Pifer, Alan.
  - Carpenter, Walter S., 1965-1967 (Box 18, Folder 26)
    Alfred P. Sloan Foundation.
  - Center for the Study of the University., 1965 (Box 18, Folder 27)
    Institute of University Administration.
  - Condolences., 1966-1967 (Box 18, Folder 28)
  - Conferences., 1966-1967 (Box 18, Folder 29)
  - Committee on Conferences., 1965-1967 (Box 18, Folder 30)
  - Congratulations and Acknowledgements., 1966 (Box 18, Folder 31)
  - Congressional and New York State Bills., 1966-1967 (Box 18, Folder 32)
  - Cornell Miscellaneous., 1965-1966 (Box 18, Folder 33)
    Morse, Chandler; Summer skill, John. United States Dept. of Health, Education and Welfare; Hampton-Cornell Cooperative Project.
  - Cornell Miscellaneous., 1965-1966 (Box 18, Folder 34)
    Rolley, William G.; Gold, Thomas. Cornell Research Park; NASA; 84" telescope.
  - Cornell Alumni Committee for Balanced Education., 1960-1967 (Box 18, Folder 35)
    Tuller, J. Daniel. Free enterprise.
  - Cornell Alumni Committee for Balanced Education., 1960-1967 (Box 18, Folder 36)
    Tuller, J. Daniel. Wings of Freedom Foundation; Free enterprise.
  - D Miscellaneous., 1965-1967 (Box 18, Folder 37)
    Day, Harold C.; Debye, Peter; Dellinger, David.
  - D Miscellaneous., 1965-1967 (Box 18, Folder 38)
    Dieckmann, Herbert; Dungan, Ralph A.; Dole, Robert; Douglas, Donald W.; Dorf, Philip; Doxiadis, Constant in; Douglas, Paul M.; Dowd, Douglas F. Dow Chemical Corporation.
  - Disadvantaged Students. Rockefeller Foundation; Negro students; Committee on Special Education Projects., 1965-1967 (Box 18, Folder 39)
  - E Miscellaneous., 1965-1967 (Box 18, Folder 40)
    Einaudi, Mario. Einaudi Foundation; Agnelli Foundation.
  - E Miscellaneous., 1965-1967 (Box 18, Folder 41)
    Ennis, Robert H.; Erwin, James A. Engineering Foundation Research Conferences.
  - F Miscellaneous., 1965-1967 (Box 19, Folder 1)
    Meyerson, Martin; Folsom, Marion B. Fayette County Fund; Academic salaries.
  - F Miscellaneous. Freeborn, Malcolm J.; Freeman, Orville L.; Friend, James A.; Fuchs, Harry Bricker; Furnas, Clifford C., 1965-1967 (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Residential Club Fire, 5 April 1967., 1967 (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Fire, 5 April 1967., 1967 (Box 19, Folder 4)
    Kurtz, Louise J. Six Year Ph.D. Program; Residential Club; Condolences
  - Fire, 5 April 1967., 1967 (Box 19, Folder 5)
    Muller, Steven. Condolences.
  - Fire, 5 April 1967., 1967 (Box 19, Folder 6)
    Condolences; News accounts.
  - Ford Foundation., 1965-1967 (Box 19, Folder 7)
    Bundy, McGeorge; McDaniel, Joseph M.; Bowles, Frank. New York State College of Agriculture, International Agricultural Development.
  - Ford Foundation., 1965-1967 (Box 19, Folder 8)
    McDaniel, Joseph M.; Bundy, McGeorge. Ford Fellowships.
  - Ford Foundation., 1965-1967 (Box 19, Folder 9)